Chris Coenen Collection on General Tom Thumb MS254
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Artifacts, 1750 -- 1996; MS254.000007
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Lavinia's calling card, London, 1888; MS254.000108 (Box 12)
    Calling card on a visit to England
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Lavinia's brothers, 1875; MS254.000109 (Box 12)
    Lavinia's brothers, identified
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Lavinia's sisters, 1875; MS254.000110 (Box 12)
    Lavinia's sisters, identified
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Lavinia and Primo having dinner, 1910; MS254.000111 (Box 12)
    Having dinner, probably in Middleboro
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Carriage, probably England, 1858; MS254.000112 (Box 12)
    Carriage
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Lavinia and man, maybe a brother, 1888; MS254.000113 (Box 12)
    Looks like one of her brothers
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Primo and Ernesto with brothers?, 1910; MS254.000114 (Box 12)
    Dressed up, maybe with Lavinia's brothers
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Woodburytype of Tam and Lavinia, 1875; MS254.000115 (Box 12)
    Tom and Lavinia
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Handbill for Lavinia's benefit for the cemetery, probably Middleboro, 1884; MS254.000116 (Box 12)
    Benefit show with Edwin Newell
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Ernesto Magri in costume, 1880; MS254.000117 (Box 12)
    In costume for a play
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Primo Magri in costume, 1880; MS254.000118 (Box 12)
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Mrs. Tom Thumb's Lilliputians ad; Adams Sisters, 1888; MS254.000119 (Box 12)
    Ad for a Company with the Adams Sisters
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Midget trio at home in Middleboro, 1910; MS254.000120 (Box 12)
    At home
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Trio at home; tea, 1910; MS254.000121 (Box 12)
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Lavinia and Primo having dinner, 1912; MS254.000122 (Box 12)
    Primo and Lavinia
  - Slide,: Middleboro Historical Society- Tom Thumb Room, 1996; MS254.000123 (Box 12)
    Displays; Bob Beal, I think
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Commodore Nutt, 1871; MS254.000124 (Box 12)
    Nutt
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lavinia Warren, 1875; MS254.000125 (Box 12)
    Mrs. Tom Thumb
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection);Commodore Nutt, 1865; MS254.000126 (Box 12)
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Commodore Nut in riding outfit, 1865; MS254.000127 (Box 12)
    Nutt set for the foxhunt
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); PT Barnum and Commodore Nutt, 1863; MS254.000128 (Box 12)
    Barnum and Nutt
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lavinia Warren in mourning, 1883; MS254.000129 (Box 12)
    Lavinia in her "widow weeds"
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Nutt reading a paper on a table, 1862; MS254.000130 (Box 12)
    Nutt reading paper with some of Tom Thumb's small furniture
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Commodore Nutt in costume, 1865; MS254.000131 (Box 12)
    Dressed in character
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Comm. Nutt and Minnie Warren dressed in character, 1865; MS254.000132 (Box 12)
    Dressed for a show
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lavinia Warren, 1863; MS254.000133 (Box 12)
    Early Lavinia
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Minnie Warren and her mother, 1865; MS254.000134 (Box 12)
    Minnie and Mrs. James Bump
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lavinia Warren, 1863; MS254.000135 (Box 12)
    Lavinia
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Tom and Lavinia, 1875; MS254.000136 (Box 12)
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Tom, Lavini, Nutt, Minnie, 1875; MS254.000137 (Box 12)
    Group
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Nutt and Minnie playing chess, 1864; MS254.000138 (Box 12)
    Playing chess
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Nutt in uniform, 1863; MS254.000139 (Box 12)
    Nutt in uniform
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Nutt dunce;The Dissappointed Nutt, 1863; MS254.000140 (Box 12)
    Nutt as the dunce; renamed after the wedding
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Anna Swan and a Circassian Woman, 1863; MS254.000141 (Box 12)
    Anna, from New Annan, Nova Scotia, started working for Barnum as a teen
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Rubber Man, 1875; MS254.000142 (Box 12)
    Wirtz, I think; photo by Eisenmann
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Annie Leaks, no arms, 1870; MS254.000143 (Box 12)
    Annie would sign her cards on the back with a poem
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Jo-o, The Dog Faced Man, 1875; MS254.000144 (Box 12)
    Theodore Jeftichew
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Tom and Lavinia in outdoor clothes, 1863; MS254.000145 (Box 12)
    Dressed for travelling
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection), 1863; MS254.000146 (Box 12)
    Lilliputian Bridegroom
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Tom as Napoleon with Lavinia, 1863; MS254.000147 (Box 12)
    Napoleon
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Group playing cards, 1863; MS254.000148 (Box 12)
    Four playing cards
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Tom Thumb in Character, 1862; MS254.000149 (Box 12)
    Tom dressed for a role
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lavinia as Bride, 1863; MS254.000150 (Box 12)
    Formal portrait
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lilliputian Card Party, 1863; MS254.000151 (Box 12)
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Nutt as Billy Barlow, 1862; MS254.000152 (Box 12)
    Nutt as a character
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Nutt and Minnie, 1873; MS254.000153 (Box 12)
    Nutt and Minnie
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Nutt dressed as guardsman, 1865; MS254.000154 (Box 12)
    Nutt in guards costume
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); George Liable as a character, 1870; MS254.000155 (Box 12)
    George Liable, friend of Thumb's
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Nutt in character as Billy Barlow, 1862; MS254.000156 (Box 12)
    Nutt in character
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Chang Eng, Siamese Twins, 1868; MS254.000157 (Box 12)
    The original Siames Twins; worked for Barnum briefly
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Goshen and Dwarf, 1865; MS254.000158 (Box 12)
    Giant Goshen and dwarf
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lavinia and Baby, Enngland, 1864; MS254.000159 (Box 12)
    Hoax baby in UK
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Group portrait, 1871; MS254.000160 (Box 12)
    Probably after the world tour
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Ernesto, Lavinia and Primo, 1895; MS254.000161 (Box 12)
    Probably taken on tour
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Tom, Lavinia and Minnie in travelling clothes, 1865; MS254.000162 (Box 12)
    Taken in England
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lavinia Warren, 1864; MS254.000163 (Box 12)
    Early portrait
  - Side: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lavinia in Reception Dress, 1863; MS254.000164 (Box 12)
    Brady
  - Side: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lavinia, 1863; MS254.000165 (Box 12)
    Brady, before the wedding
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Tom as Napoleon and Lavinia, 1863; MS254.000166 (Box 12)
    Tom as Napoleon
  - Side: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lavinia before the wedding, 1863; MS254.000167 (Box 12)
    Before the wedding
  - Side: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lavinia early, 1863; MS254.000168 (Box 12)
  - Side: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Colored version of Lavinia, 1863; MS254.000169 (Box 12)
    Hand colored
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lavinia pre- wedding, 1863; MS254.000170 (Box 12)
    By a chair
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Early Lavinia, 1863; MS254.000171 (Box 12)
    Lavinia Warren
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Minnie Warren, 1863; MS254.000172 (Box 12)
    Minnie Warren
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Minnie and probably sister, 1863; MS254.000173 (Box 12)
    Minnie, probably with one of her sisters
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Copy of a dag of Tom Thumb, 1850; MS254.000174 (Box 12)
    Copy of an earlier photo of Tom
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Primo, Lavinia, George Liable, Mrs. Liable, Ernesto Magri, 1886; MS254.000175 (Box 12)
    Group in Middleboro
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Jennie Quigley, 1875; MS254.000176 (Box 12)
    Jennie with fan
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lavinia in Middleboro, 1880; MS254.000177 (Box 12)
    Lavinia by Putnam
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Unusual side view of Lavinia, 1875; MS254.000178 (Box 12)
    Lavinia by Sherman & McHugh of NY
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lucia Zarate and mother, 1880; MS254.000179 (Box 12)
    Young Lucia Zarate
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); The Disappointed Nutt, 1863; MS254.000180 (Box 12)
    Com. Nutt
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Nutt reading on little chairs, 1863; MS254.000181 (Box 12)
    Nutt reading the paper
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Princess Paulina, begging, 1894; MS254.000182 (Box 12)
    Paulina on bended knee; maybe manager
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lavinia by a table and book, 1865; MS254.000183 (Box 12)
    Rare photo of Lavinia
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Composite of photos of Tom and Lavinia, 1863; MS254.000184 (Box 12)
    Composite, probably by Anthony
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lavinia with Tom as Napoleon, 1863; MS254.000185 (Box 12)
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Tom sitting in a chair, 1863; MS254.000186 (Box 12)
    Tom sitting in a normal size chair
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); PT Barnum and Tom Thumb; LSC, 1858; MS254.000187 (Box 12)
    Tom in London with Barnum
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Tom and Lavinia and Man, maybe a manager, 1863; MS254.000188 (Box 12)
    Unknown man
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Early Lavinia in quilted dress, 1863; MS254.000189 (Box 12)
    Nice dress
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Tom by Putnam, Middleboro, 1880; MS254.000190 (Box 12)
    Tom Thumb by Putnam
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Tom Thumb and Comm. Nutt in character, 1864; MS254.000191 (Box 12)
    Tom and Nutt dressed for a play
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Portrait of Charles Stratton; Tom Thumb, 1878; MS254.000192 (Box 12)
    Portrait
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Portrait of Tom by Putnam, 1880; MS254.000193 (Box 12)
    Another portrait of Tom by Putnam
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Nutt reading, same as 1204, 1863; MS254.000194 (Box 12)
    Copy of 1204
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Charles Nestel and Comm. Foote in character, 1868; MS254.000195 (Box 12)
    Charles Nestel
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Fat Lady, Madame Sherwood, 1865; MS254.000196 (Box 12)
    Madame Sherwood
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Unknown midget woman, 1880; MS254.000197 (Box 12)
    Dawrf woman
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Early Nutt and Minnie, 1863; MS254.000198 (Box 12)
    Young Nutt and Minnie just before the wedding
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Adams Sisters fro Martha's Vineyard, 1882; MS254.000199 (Box 12)
    Friends of Lavinia
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Lavinia in reception dress, 1863; MS254.000200 (Box 12)
    Reception dress
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Admiral Dot as Policeman, 1882; MS254.000201 (Box 12)
    Admiral Dot in a role as policeman
  - Slide: HTC (Harvard Theatre Collection); Comm. Nutt, or maybe Admiral Dot, in a role, 1882; MS254.000202 (Box 12)
    Nutt or Dot dressed for a role
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Commodore Nutt in costume on table, 1863; MS254.000203 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Commodore Nutt in uniform, 1863; MS254.000204 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Albino Family, 1865; MS254.000205 (Box 12)
    Albino performers
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Portrait of Mercy Lavinia Warren Bump Stratton, 1875; MS254.000206 (Box 12)
    Formal portrait of Lavinia
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Portrait of Charles Sherwood Stratton, 1875; MS254.000207 (Box 12)
    Formal portrait of Charles
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Leopard Boy; Benamin Ashbury; piebald black boy, 1875; MS254.000208 (Box 12)
    Sideshow performer
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Turtle Boy; George Williams, 1875; MS254.000209 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Fanny Mills; Ohio Big Foot Woman, 1875; MS254.000210 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Fred Wilson; Lobster Boy, 1875; MS254.000211 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Avery Chicos; Frog Boy, 1875; MS254.000212 (Box 12)
    SIdeshow performer
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Felix Wehrle; Elastic Skin Man, 1875; MS254.000213 (Box 12)
    SIdeshow performer;; Ehlers-Danlos Syndrome
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Felix Wehrle; Elastic Skin Man, 1875; MS254.000214 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Aztecs; pinheads, 1875; MS254.000215 (Box 12)
    Micro-cephalic
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Deformed baby, 1875; MS254.000216 (Box 12)
    Deformed baby
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Chauncy Morlan; fat boy; nude, 1875; MS254.000217 (Box 12)
    Naked Chauncy
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Chauncy Morlan; fat boy; nude, 1875; MS254.000218 (Box 12)
    Rear view
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Chauncy Morlan; fat boy; nude, 1875; MS254.000219 (Box 12)
    Reclining
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Chauncy Morlan; fat boy; nude, 1875; MS254.000220 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Adams Sisters; Martha's Vineyard, 1873; MS254.000221 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Jo-Jo, The Dog Faced Boy, 1875; MS254.000222 (Box 12)
    Hypertrichosis
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Magri Brothers with man, 1878; MS254.000223 (Box 12)
    Maybe manager
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Magri Brothers with man, 1878; MS254.000224 (Box 12)
    Early Magri
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; PT Barnum, 1863; MS254.000225 (Box 12)
    Barnum
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Hairy People, 1875; MS254.000226 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Chauncy Morlan; fat boy; nude, 1875; MS254.000227 (Box 12)
    With pants
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Hairy man and child, 1875; MS254.000228 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Comm.Nutt and Minnie Warren; London, 1864; MS254.000229 (Box 12)
    LSC
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Elephants, 1868; MS254.000230 (Box 12)
    Unknown location
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Myrtle Corbin; four legs, 1870; MS254.000231 (Box 12)
    Incomplete Siamese twin
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Armless artist, 1875; MS254.000232 (Box 12)
    Armless
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Lavinia, 1863; MS254.000233 (Box 12)
    Before wedding
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Lavinia, traveling clothes, 1863; MS254.000234 (Box 12)
    Winter clothes
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Lavinia on chair, 1863; MS254.000235 (Box 12)
    Sitting on a chair
  - Slide: Syracuse U., Becker Collection; Lavinia in quilted dress, 1863; MS254.000236 (Box 12)
    Checkered dress
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Uffner's midgets meet queen, 1880; MS254.000237 (Box 12)
    From a pamphlet
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Uffner's midgets meet queen, 1880; MS254.000238 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Leonine, 1870; MS254.000239 (Box 12)
    Hairy lady
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Uffner's Royal American Midgets, 1870; MS254.000240 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Older Tom comparing height, 1880; MS254.000241 (Box 12)
    Uffner's ad
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Uffner's Giant, 1880; MS254.000242 (Box 12)
    Uffner ad
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Daisy and Violet Hilton poster, 1920; MS254.000243 (Box 12)
    Ad for Twins
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Jumbo loading 1, 1882; MS254.000244 (Box 12)
    Loading Jumbo for the trip to America
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Jumbo loading 2, 1882; MS254.000245 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Jumbo loading 3, 1882; MS254.000246 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Jumbo loading 4, 1882; MS254.000247 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Chang, Chinese giant, 1880; MS254.000248 (Box 12)
    Chang
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Tom carriage article, 1858; MS254.000249 (Box 12)
    Photo
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; British baby article, 1864; MS254.000250 (Box 12)
    Article with photo
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Elastic Man, 1890; MS254.000251 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Jo-Jo, Dog Faced Man, 1890; MS254.000252 (Box 12)
    From article
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Egyptian Hall with Tom's carriage, 1845; MS254.000253 (Box 12)
    Print
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Egyptian Hall movies, 1910; MS254.000254 (Box 12)
    Later view
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Egyptian Hall without Tom's carriage, 1845; MS254.000255 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Early Museum, NY, 1840; MS254.000256 (Box 12)
    print
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Lavinia, London, 1910; MS254.000257 (Box 12)
    Signed
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Primo, London, 1910; MS254.000258 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; British baby, article, 1864; MS254.000259 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Wedding Group, 1863; MS254.000260 (Box 12)
    Vignette
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Early Magri Brothers, 1875; MS254.000261 (Box 12)
    Probably in Europe
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; French cartoon about Tom Thumb, 1867; MS254.000262 (Box 12)
    Full page cartoons
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Tom meets Royal Family, 1845; MS254.000263 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Ad for Tom Thumb in London, Baby, 1844; MS254.000264 (Box 12)
    Poster
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Ad for Thumb's in London; Baby, 1864; MS254.000265 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Millie-Christine, Siamese Twins, 1868; MS254.000266 (Box 12)
    Twins
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; Millie-Christine, Siamese Twins, 1872; MS254.000267 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham;James Morris, Elastic Skin Man, 1890; MS254.000268 (Box 12)
    Brochure
  - Slide: Mander & Mitchenson, Beckenham; James Morris, Elastic Skin Man, 1890; MS254.000269 (Box 12)
    Brochure, photo
  - Slide: Wisconsin Historical Society: Print of Tom Thumb Wedding, 1863 -- 1890; MS254.000270 (Box 12)
    Fanciful print of the wedding made at a later date
  - Slide: Circus World Museum: Circus Poster with Barnum and Tom and Lavinia, 1881; MS254.000271 (Box 12)
    Poster made for the 1881 circus that included the Strattons
  - Slide: Circus World Museum; Detail of poster showing Tom Thumb's House, 1881; MS254.000272 (Box 12)
    Not really Tom Thumb's House
  - Slide: Circus World Museum: Detail of poster showing Tom and Lavinia, 1881; MS254.000273 (Box 12)
    As they looked when they joined the circus for a season
  - Slide: Circus World Museum: Circus poster with Barnum and Tom and Lavinia, 1881; MS254.000274 (Box 12)
    Larger view
  - Slide: Circus World Museum: Poster for Jumbo's Arrival to US, 1882; MS254.000275 (Box 12)
    Poster announcing the arrival of Jumbo
  - Slide: Circus World Museum: Myrtle Corbin, 1870; MS254.000276 (Box 12)
    Early cdv of Myrtle Corbin, incomplete Siamese twin
  - Slide: Circus World Museum: Myrtle Corbin, 1910; MS254.000277 (Box 12)
    Could be later; Myrtle, Husband and Daughter
  - Print: Circus World Museum: Tom Thumb in Masonic Regalia, 1880; MS254.000278 (Box 12)
    Tom was a devoted Mason
  - Print: National Gallery of Canada; Tom Thumb Daguerreotype, 1848; MS254.000279 (Box 12)
    Dag of Tom about age ten
  - Print: Hertzberg Circus Museum; Tom Thumb and man; dag copy, 1848; MS254.000280 (Box 12)
    Dag of Tom with uknown man
  - Print: Hertzberg Circus Museum; Tom Thumb Dag, 1848; MS254.000281 (Box 12)
    Dag of Tom Thumb that disappeared from the collection in the 1950's and re-surfaced at a Swann Galleries auction in 1996
  - Print: Hertzberg Circus Museum: Swann catalog with copy of Tom Thumb Dag on back, 1848 -- 1996; MS254.000282 (Box 12)
    Sold for $12,000 to W. Schaefer
  - Print: Hertzberg Circus Collection: Tom Thumb and Mother, 1848; MS254.000283 (Box 12)
    Dag of Tom and his mother
  - Print: Hertzberg Circus Collection: Tom Thumb's Carriage, 1858; MS254.000284 (Box 12)
    Probably from a cdv in UK
  - Slide: Mrs. Tom Thumb's Carriage, 1890; MS254.000285 (Box 12)
    From an album
  - Slide: Ernesto, Primo and Lavinia, 1890; MS254.000286 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Ernesto Magri, 1890; MS254.000287 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Ernesto and Primo swordfighting, 1890; MS254.000288 (Box 12)
  - Slide; George Eastman House; Tom Thumb and Parents Dag, 1850; MS254.000289 (Box 12)
    From an auction catalog
  - Slide: George Eastman House: Tom as Robinson Crusoe ambrotype, 1855; MS254.000290 (Box 12)
  - Slide: George Eastman House: Tom as Highlander ambrotype, 1855; MS254.000291 (Box 12)
  - Newspaper copy: Lavinia, Primo and Ernesto with the Gentry Bros, Show, 1907; MS254.000292 (Box 12)
    Photo of the three at the circus
  - Newspaper copy: Article about Lavinia joining Gentry Bros. Show, 1907; MS254.000293 (Box 12)
    Very inaccurate article about Lavinia
  - Print: National Portrait Gallery: Dag of P.T. Barnum and Tom Thumb, 1850; MS254.000294 (Box 12)
    Famous dag of Tom and Barnum by Root
  - Print: National Portrait Gallery: Wedding group; Brady, 1863; MS254.000295 (Box 12)
    From the original negative
  - Print: Barnum Museum: Dag of Tom as Napoleon, 1843; MS254.000296 (Box 12)
    Early dag of Tom as Napoleon
  - Print: Barnum Museum: Dag of Tom and Father, 1843; MS254.000297 (Box 12)
    Early dag of Charles Stratton and Sherwood Stratton
  - Print:Connecticut Historical Society: Copy of a Dag of Tom Thumb, 1850; MS254.000298 (Box 12)
    Dag of Tom Thumb
  - Slide: Conn. Hist, Soc,: Print Tom and Lavinia meet Victoria, 1880; MS254.000299 (Box 12)
    From a brochure; Tom and Lavinia look as they dis in 1881; but were not in England at the time
  - Slide: Conn. Hist, Soc,: Print Tom and Lavinia's Wedding, 1863; MS254.000300 (Box 12)
    From a brochure
  - Slide; Conn. Hist. Soc.: Tom Thumb's House in Bridgeport, 1860; MS254.000301 (Box 12)
    From a brochure about Tom's life; house, if it ever existed; is gone
  - Slide: Conn. Hist. Soc.: Barnum's American Museum print, 1855; MS254.000302 (Box 12)
    Print of the Museum
  - Slide: Conn. Hist. Soc.: Barnum's American ad, 1855; MS254.000303 (Box 12)
  - Slise: Conn. Hist. Soc.: Print of Tom in his characters before the Crowned Heads, 1858; MS254.000304 (Box 12)
    Tom's characters
  - Slide: Conn. Hist. Soc.: Ad for Barnum's American Museum, 1855; MS254.000305 (Box 12)
    Nice print of Museum
  - Slide: Conn. Hist. Soc.: Lavinia just before wedding, 1863; MS254.000306 (Box 12)